(Penny:)Hey, Leonard, check this out.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, she's doing it again.
(Leonard:)I think it upsets Sheldon
when you play with the food.
(Sheldon:)No, it upsets Sheldon when she
willy-nilly takes it from the containers...
(Sheldon:)...without regard
for its equitable distribution.
(Sheldon:)This is essentially
why you have famine in India.
(Penny:)You want me to put it back?
(Bernadette:)-Leonard?
-It upsets Sheldon...
(Leonard:)...when you play with the Sheldon.
(Howard(arriving):)What's up, my nerdizzles?
(Howard(arriving):)Raj, Sheldon, I want you
to meet my girlfriend, Bernadette.
(Sheldon:)-Hello.
-Leonard, Penny.
(Howard:)-You know my girlfriend, Bernadette.
-Yeah. Hey.
(Howard(arriving):)Bernadette,
say "fo'shizzle" to my nerdizzles.
(Bernadette:)I don't think I can.
(Bernadette:)I don't have Howard's street cred.
I hope it's all right, I told Bernadette
she could join us for dinner.
(Leonard:)-Sure. The more, the merrier.
-No, that's a false equivalency.
(Sheldon:)More does not equal merry.
(Sheldon:)If there were 2000 people in this apartment,
would we be celebrating?
(Sheldon:)No, we'd be suffocating.
(Leonard:)-Sheldon.
-Don't "Sheldon" me.
(Sheldon:)-We ordered for five people, not six.
-It's fine.
We'll put it on the table, family-style.
Oh, sure. Why don't we put our hands
behind our backs...
(Sheldon:)...have an old-fashioned
eating contest?
(Leonard:)Relax. It'll be fine. Sit down, you guys.
ALL EXCEPT BERNADETTE: No.
-What?
(Penny:)Oh, yeah, you can't sit there.
(Bernadette:)-Why not?
-That's where Sheldon sits.
(Bernadette:)He can't sit somewhere else?
In the winter, that seat's close enough
to the radiator...
...so he's warm
yet not so close that he sweats.
(Penny:)In the summer,
it's in the path of a breeze...
(Penny:)...created by opening windows there.
(Penny:)It faces the television at an angle
that isn't direct so he can talk...
(Penny:)...yet not so wide
that the picture looks distorted.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps there's hope for you after all.